[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "ISPIRITO: It looks like chocolates, it looks like the worst food you can eat, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "It's like pasta.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What was the total calorie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Let's see if the audience can guess how many calories in all of these foods.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Tangerine, how many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "500.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Andrei, how many?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "50.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Well, what it actually was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "So, this a high protein chocolate smoothy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "And normally, you assume a lot of calories, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, normally, the pasta is made with flour which is almost 300 calories in and of itself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "How many calories?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "OK, so that would be about 710.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "How do you culturally change that kind of thinking and the fast food epidemic and so on to get them to start to cook at home in a way that can produce this kind of result?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "It's an unbelievably difficult question to answer, but I think what we're doing right now is part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "You have better sex or your food, Rocco?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I'll tell you what, the reasons I got obvious is my sex wasn't as good as it should be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rocco"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "One (ph) faster, so, how old are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "``", "NN", ":", "JJR", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "I'm 46 years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "You're 6 foot, 1 right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "You were -- your heaviest, how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Almost 230, 228, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "And what did you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "I was 35 years old, and I was already being told that I'm in health danger of heart disease.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "CC", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "You lost how much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "40 pounds and -- so if a chubby chef with crooked spine and flat feet, who could totally get away with it, by the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Jared, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "So, you're this unknown guy who just announced he'd been eating a lot of Subways and had lost a lot of weight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Do you still eat Subway sandwiches?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I do, you know, I don't eat it every single day anymore, but I've learned a lot, you know, in my -- exactly in moderation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Piers, my heaviest weight was 320.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "And how do you do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "So, I was like a business guy running around the world, doing deals focused on building companies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "How have you managed to stay so disciplined?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "So, the first thing I'd say, Piers, is I didn't look at what I did as a diet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Why did you want to do that, why do you want to become me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I don't know if it's so much you, but I felt like I needed a different perspective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Because you've never been fat, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I've never been overweight, never struggled.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Is there something you find that that wasn't happening if (inaudible) you've lost it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I think some people look at me differently.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Oh, Drew, you've lost it, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "No one was really mean, but I felt like, from my perspective, people were staring at me more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "How do we change the thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I've heard so often people trying to blame of people for those problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Why are you seeing so much business, you think, form the stories that you get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "From the stories that I hear, it's very clear that people are addicted to sugar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "When it gets to that stage, people are pretty desperate, aren't they, to do something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Well, our whole country is desperate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "How we get through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "And the reality of it is it's making you sick whether you have a weight problem or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Tracy, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I'm great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "So every time I see one of these celebrities having a baby, within about three months, they look like (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "What do you do to these poor women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "You know what, I support them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "I think we gave then -- didn't we give them DVD's?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well that's a little surprise actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["DVD"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNP", ":", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What are the key things that women who've had a baby need to do quite quickly to get rid of the baby fat and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Well, right now Kim (ph) is doing what she should be doing which is bonding with her baby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What kind of workout should you be doing and what kind of diet should you combine it with, if you want to just get some reasonable results, you know, maybe lose 89 pounds or whatever it may be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Yeah, that's a really great question, because the formula is key and the ratio is key and also enjoying life is key.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "What is it about your Barry's Bootcamp that is different to others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "It's the best combination, both?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Now, what is it and how does it work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "It's indoor cycling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "How do you get people into right discipline, to keep going and not just give up after a few weeks because so many people do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Well, I think that's the main thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "And what is unique about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "What's unique about it is that, you know, well, first of all, I'd like to say that people are afraid to workout and because they think it's so hard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "What is a modifier?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "A modifier, if someone so -- if I'm doing crazy high jumps, there's a modifier doing a less low impact.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "And how many times a week to get reasonably fit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Actually, that's a good question because I'm a believer in the hour workout.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Barry, you want to get a free plug-in while you're on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "You know, if I can also say, it has to be fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "So, this is like a bike, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "It's a bike.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "hen what happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "I want you to look at that little screen and I want you to take your torque to 25.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "his one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Until it gets to 25.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "You're at 25, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "You good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "Easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "How's that going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "It's easy (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140110pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "And how many seconds we'll have to keep doing this for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "About 30.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]